today if something happens to my vehicle
and it goes to the workshop so for
example it's a major loss and every
sixth or seventh uh day of my month I'll
be paying my car Emi and for example if
the vehicle is in the workshop for more
than 30 days or 40 days so that Emi
whatever I am paying for example you
take it as ten thousand or fifteen
thousand so that Emi which is that that
will be covered under this Emi product
so when customer can opt key up to how
many emis he can take like from one Emi
to six EMA he has the option
all those things can be done
if Suppose there is any claim in one
vehicle okay so that way till NCB will
not miss that vehicle claim will not
affect the entity of the other two
vehicles what if I sell that one vehicle
now we can do it cycle complaints online
only if I'm sitting here at home only
you will get a complete number and share
with us and the amount which has been
the fraud or identity loss whatever
so amount of what you have lost you have
to buy the summer shoot that for season
from 50 000 Rupees to we have Cruise so
you will have to pay us for that it
starts with 2000 rupees for 50. my
credit card limit is one lakh rupees so
I should buy online rupees limit maximum
for uh for somebody what happens is
nowadays we have seen uh one of the
incident availability I've seen we have
used in a launch in airport and when we
landed in uh one of the country we could
see that there was a fraud of four line
rupees was swiped from the card because
some I mean the hackers are so smart
that they track you where you are going
know that your mobile is Switched Off
for otp's for such a long time when we
landed in an airport Wi-Fi we saw that
emails not messages
number was not working so I mean there's
this people who work on that so you will
have to take a policy based upon your
liability what how much what do you have
to includes the data so what if it
really covers is the neglect
a particular customer or a corporate is
negligent in rendering services to the
client and the client is not satisfied
with the level of services you are
providing to them he can find a loss
against you that is typically what it
covers
so